export const QuizData = [
    {
        question: "When setState()  is called inside render() method, which of the following events takes place?",
        options:[ "stackoverflow java error", "stackoverflow in error", "stackoverflow error", "JavaScript"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "State whether true or false: React.js covers only the view layer of the app.",
        options:["true", "false"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "The function which is called to render HTML to a web page in react?",
        options: ["rander()", "rander_DOM()", "reacetDOM_rander()", "DOM_HTML"],
        answer: 1
    },
    { question: "Who is the creator of JavaScript?", 
      options: ["Brendan Eich", "Tim Berners-Lee", "James Gosling", "none of the above"], 
      answer: 0 },
      {
        question: "When setState()  is called inside render() method, which of the following events takes place?",
        options:[ "stackoverflow java error", "stackoverflow in error", "stackoverflow error", "JavaScript"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "State whether true or false: React.js covers only the view layer of the app.",
        options:["true", "false"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "The function which is called to render HTML to a web page in react?",
        options: ["rander()", "rander_DOM()", "reacetDOM_rander()", "DOM_HTML"],
        answer: 1
    },
    { question: "Who is the creator of JavaScript?", 
      options: ["Brendan Eich", "Tim Berners-Lee", "James Gosling", "none of the above"], 
      answer: 0 },

    { question: "Which company developed JavaScript?", 
      options: ["Microsoft", "Netscape", "Sun Microsystems", "none of the above"], 
      answer: 1 },
    
    { question: "What was the original name of JavaScript?", 
        options: ["Mocha", "ECMAScript", "LiveScript", "none of the above"], 
        answer: 2 },
    
    { question: "Which of the following is a correct way to declare a variable in JavaScript?", 
        options: ["let varName;", "declare varName;", "var varName;", "none of the above"], 
        answer: 2 },
    
    { question: "JavaScript is an implementation of which standard?", 
        options: ["HTML5", "ECMAScript", "DOM", "none of the above"], 
        answer: 1 },

    { question: "Which company developed JavaScript?", 
      options: ["Microsoft", "Netscape", "Sun Microsystems", "none of the above"], 
      answer: 1 },
    
    { question: "What was the original name of JavaScript?", 
        options: ["Mocha", "ECMAScript", "LiveScript", "none of the above"], 
        answer: 2 },
    
    { question: "Which of the following is a correct way to declare a variable in JavaScript?", 
        options: ["let varName;", "declare varName;", "var varName;", "none of the above"], 
        answer: 2 },
    
    { question: "JavaScript is an implementation of which standard?", 
        options: ["HTML5", "ECMAScript", "DOM", "none of the above"], 
        answer: 1 },
];